webook.com 2016-10-31

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting [http://www.WEbook.com](http://www.webook.com/) (together with all content on the site and other websites operated by WEbook Inc. or its affiliates ("WEbook") (the "Site")). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy is part of the WEbook Terms of Use and Member Agreement ("Agreement"), which is a binding agreement between all Members of the Site and WEbook. The defined terms in the Agreement have the same meaning in this Privacy Policy.

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on the Site and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, at WEBook’s discretion for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of the Privacy Policy will be identified by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

The current version of the Privacy Policy is available at http://www.WEbook.com/privacy.aspx. You may also review Archived Versions of the Privacy Policy.

## Introduction

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any Personal Information that WEBook requests from its Members.

Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal Information in order to have access to certain information available on our Site. However, in order to provide you with the services available on the Site, including but not limited to participating in forums, contributing synopses, comments, plots, character descriptions, scripts, ratings, etc., you must register with WEbook and create an account ("Account") and provide us with your email address, a pen name, birth date and a password that you will use for your Account. We shall then send you an email to your email address to instruct you how to confirm your registration.

We may request additional Personal Information from time to time, particularly as necessary to publish a Work or obtain copyright registration for a Work.

If you have an Account you may, if you wish, add more information about yourself.

Please note that Content is not considered Personal Information subject to this Privacy Policy.

## The Way We Use Personal Information

If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site, we will use your Personal Information to improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and authenticate your access to the Site's services you are authorized to use.

Your Pen name and any content you make, place or post on the Site may become publicly available. Content that you make, place, or post on the Site may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels or published as part of a book, and may be viewed by the general public. Copyright and licensing issues related to Content are, as noted above, covered in greater detail in the Agreement.

We may transfer your Personal Information within WEbook or to WEbook's third-party service providers, but only to provide services on the Site or to you, across borders, and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.

If you approve in advance or if you use your real name as you pen name, WEbook may use and display your real name on the Site.

The Agreement also has provisions about how WEbook may use your Personal Information in connection with publishing Content, crediting a Member’s authorship of Content, registering copyrights in Content, and other purposes related to Company’s business.

We may provide Personal Information and non-personally-identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and attempt to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

You acknowledge and agree that your Personal Information is covered by the Archival License set forth in the Agreement.

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Site pages utilize "cookies" and other tracking technologies. A "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by a Site user. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them.

You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you will need to re-enter certain identifying information, should we in the future require such information, to gain access to certain parts of the Site.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Site and your web experience.

## Notice

Except as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not currently provide your Personal Information to third parties, except for third parties who may perform services on the Site or to you. Nevertheless, we may at a later time choose to make certain offers or services available to our users from third parties. If we do, during the registration process and at certain points thereafter in connection with specific offers, we may ask you whether your Personal Information may be sent to third parties who have products, services and opportunities which may be useful to you. If you give your permission to allow third parties to contact you, your Personal Information (such as your contact information and other information collected during your visit to our Site) may be shared with data aggregators, marketers (possibly in the form of list rental), and other organizations. WEbook does not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on WEbook's behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Regardless of your decision regarding the sharing of your Personal Information, we may share broad aggregate demographic data and related usage information with our business partners. This aggregate information does not contain any Personal Information that can identify an individual user.

## Choice

You may choose whether or not to provide certain Personal Information to WEbook. The notices we will provide where WEbook collects Personal Information on the Site should help you to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal Information we request, you can still visit most of the Site, but you may be unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve our interaction with you.

## Security

We have implemented suitable security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the Personal Information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors that have access to, and are associated with the processing of your Personal Information, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of your information.

## Access/Accuracy

We wish to make sure that your Personal Information is accurate. You may check your profile and email us at "legal at WEbook dot com" to add information, correct any incorrect information and delete information.

## Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites

Our Site may use a reputable third party to present or serve advertisements that you may see at our Site. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site may contain links to other sites. Other sites may also reference or link to our Site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.

## Children's Privacy

The Site is not structured to attract children under the age of 13. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 13 years of age.

## In the Event of Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that WEbook is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the Personal Information we have collected from our users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.

## Special Note to International Users

The Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are a user accessing the Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and the Agreement, you are transferring your Personal Information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

## Commitment

We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and WEbook's Sites are constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us at "legal at WEbook dot com." While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities as soon as possible.

When you send email or other communication to WEbook, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests, and improve our services.

## Your Consent

By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy and to WEbook's processing of Personal Information for the purposes given above and in the Agreement. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes.

## Your California Privacy Rights

WEbook's Privacy Policy is to share Personal Information only with the owner's informed consent. With your consent, from time-to-time, WEbook may provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know. If you have further inquires regarding WEbook's Information Sharing Practices, please let us know. The designated contact for these queries is legal at WEbook dot com.

Last modified: February 12, 2008
